Excuse me sir.
Hello.
Sir.
Yes.
Quick question for you.
Yes sir.
Have you ever been broke before?
Oh yes.
Yeah?
I have.
In what line of business are you in?
I'm in the shoe business.
Are you a business owner?
I am.
What's the name of your company?
Steve Madden.
Steve Added?
Are you Steve Added?
I am.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
You really don't want to know that.
How much?
It's a big number.
Give me a number.
About two and a half billion in sales.
Question for you.
What's up?
Real quick, real quick.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yeah, I've been broke many times.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
Probably 12 to 15 million.
Best trades I ever made
was a couple of years back.
Amazon.
That was my cash cow.
Did you make a lot of money off of Amazon?
I did.
What do billionaires do differently
than 99% of other people?
Guys, we are in Billionaires Row right now.
This is the wealthiest street
in all of New York City.
Home to where the largest percentage,
the largest capita of billionaires lives.
So we're going to be walking
around trying to go find billionaires,
see how they became wealthy.
And how you can follow their
blueprint and do the exact same thing.
Let's go find them and
see what they have to say.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
Broke?
Yeah.
No.
No?
But what line of business did you end up in?
I am in the construction business.
Did you own a company?
I own a company.
Yeah.
How long?
35 years.
I started a channel at the University of Texas.
I grew it to 9 million followers.
And I go all over the country.
What are you doing?
What's that?
Instagram.
Yeah.
I'm going to show them.
I'm going to ask them a couple questions.
What were you building?
I build these towers.
Actually?
I build them all over from Philly down to Miami.
What was the most amount of money that
you made in a single year at your business?
The most amount in one year?
You really don't want to know that.
How much?
It's a big number.
Give me a number.
$30 million.
That's for yourself?
Yeah.
How about for the business?
Several hundred.
Several hundred million?
Several hundred, yeah.
Like more than $200 million?
What's that?
More than $200 million?
Yes.
Not more than $500 million?
Huh?
More than $500 million?
In that area.
$500 million.
That's incredible.
As a multiple nine-figure entrepreneur, what was
the best financial advice that you ever received?
If you can recall one lesson you learned.
Just stay involved.
What do you mean by that?
Don't delegate too much.
Stay involved.
But some people say that if you don't delegate enough, then
you can work in the business and not on the business.
That's not it.
Just stay involved.
If you delegate, people respect what you inspect.
Just check it out.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No.
What was the turning point to financial freedom?
What did you see that
made you want to stand out?
Just that I'm an entrepreneur.
I have a real estate business.
I have a manufacturing business.
I have a construction business.
So you diversified.
Yeah, yeah.
A lot of people say
just focus on one thing, though.
No, never.
Why not?
Never.
Maybe one wife.
That's about it.
One wife?
That's about it?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a great salesman.
What was your secret to selling?
I know how to close a deal.
What's the secret to closing?
I know what deal not to do.
I know who not to talk to.
And would you say that's just as important as—
It's all in sync.
Before you sit down, make sure
you know who you're debating against.
Because there's better guys.
Why risk it?
Don't take high-risk bets.
One thing, high-risk bets go to Vegas, you know?
See you later.
Have a great day, guys.
Thank you.
Appreciate that.
You guys, we just interviewed a construction mogul out here.
New York City.
He's done multiple hundreds of millions
of dollars in a single year.
That was a beautiful interview right there.
My favorite part, my best takeaway from
that interview was when we talked about sales.
He says, I know exactly what deals not to do.
A lot of people, they get greedy, they
get desperate, and they go into the wrong deals
and the wrong business.
Great interview out here in New York City.
We got to keep it
rolling and go get another one.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
Yes.
Quick question for you.
Yes, sir.
Have you ever been broke before?
Oh, yes.
Yeah?
I have.
In what line of business are you in?
I'm in the shoe business.
Are you a business owner?
I am.
What's the name of your company?
Steve Madden.
Steve Added?
Are you Steve Added?
I am.
Actually, real quick, I started
the channel in Austin, Texas.
I grew it to 9 million followers.
I go all over the country just asking
business owners their best advice to new entrepreneurs.
But I get one quick minute with you real quick.
What would you like to know?
So how long have you been a business owner for?
34 years.
Over these 34 years, in terms of revenue,
what was the most amount of money that you've
made in a single year?
Our company, I think it does a
little over about $2.5 billion in sales.
$2.5 billion.
I think so.
I don't even follow it.
Let me ask you this, though.
As somebody who's running one of the biggest
shoe companies in the world, what's your best
advice to anybody trying to build their
business into a billion-dollar company like Steve Madden?
Oh my God.
Get a lot of help.
Raise a lot of money.
You got to trust your partners, I guess.
But if you make something people want, you'll be okay.
Did you have a lot of
money when you started this business?
I started with $1,100.
How important was focus for you in one industry?
You know, I started working in
a shoe store when I was 16.
So I've kind of been,
that's sort of been my thing.
What's more important?
Product or distribution?
Product is everything.
Why is that?
Because without that, you have, it doesn't matter.
All the distribution in the world doesn't matter.
What was the lowest point
in your career as an entrepreneur?
I did some time in prison.
That was pretty bad.
And I've had a very good run.
I've been very fortunate.
Knowing what you don't know is such a gift.
And then you're able to get help, you know?
So that's sort of the secret.
Well, it's not a secret anymore.
I really appreciate that.
Okay, good.
Thank you, sir.
Guys, we just ran into an interviewed billionaire,
Steve Madden, and we're headed to go get our
next interview right now.
But I don't think you guys realize, guys,
he's built one of the biggest brands in the
entire world.
And one of the things that comes up time
and time again, when I interview the most successful
entrepreneurs is the importance of
building your brand in all aspects.
But in today's world, especially your online
presence, one of the most important components
of this is securing a
strong domain name for your business.
So let's be real guys.
Finding a good.com domain these days is amazing.
But sometimes it's even more
important than finding a domain name.
And that's because the domain name is so important.
It's even more important than finding
the domain name that you need.
And that's why I recommend using a .online domain.
Unlike .com, .online has a
huge inventory of available names.
So you're much more likely to get the
domain that you want, whether you're launching a
business, offering various services or even
freelancing .online works for any industry.
And since the word online is searched
500 million times a month globally, you're instantly
tapping into a massive audience.
And here's the thing, guys.
It's only 99 cents for the first year.
And if you're serious about taking your business
to the next level, securing the right domain
is everything.
So use code SOHK to get your .online domain
for just 99 cents for the first year by heading
over to www.get.onlineslashsohk2.
We're usually link down in the description of
this video, but with that being said, let's
go get this next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Yeah.
Question for you real quick.
Real quick.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yeah.
I've been broke many times.
And what line of business did you end up in?
I've worked in real estate, I was in construction.
Yeah, have you ever been a business owner?
I am a business owner.
What type of company?
I'm an independent contractor
and I own an electronics business.
Actually.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, actually right.
I started a channel in Austin,
we grew it to nine million followers.
I interview business owners all over the country
on the best advice to new entrepreneurs.
Can I get one quick minute with you real quick?
Yeah, you can get a minute, yeah.
So you've owned a bunch of different businesses.
Sure have.
Let me ask you this, across all these companies,
in one year, in terms of revenue,
what was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
When I was in construction, scrap iron,
we were barging scrap steel in New Jersey
and we had a barge and a shredder
and it was quite an operation.
Yearly, probably 12 to 15 mil.
12 to 15 million.
Million, yeah.
That's incredible.
Best financial decision you ever made?
Probably to buy a two-story apartment
and refurbish it and rent it,
let it pay the mortgage and leverage it for credit.
So you created a lot of wealth through real estate.
Sure have, real estate's a good deal, man.
Thank you, my friend. Can't miss it, man.
Real estate, energy's good too.
Why energy?
Ah, this is a long story.
We're done.
I promise you this'll be so worth it.
Did you go to college?
I went to college, but college was not
where I got my information.
It was from mentorship and being in a family business
in the trenches with people that were doing it
and watching them work and staying by their side.
What's one lesson about business
you'd give to somebody they will not learn in school?
Any college.
Let's say he doesn't want to go.
You have to have a PhD in communication.
You have to be able to articulate
and be able to communicate
effectively, communication.
You don't get that from a scholastic education.
You get that with dealing
with real people in real time
and going through difficult situations
and learning how to make those adjustments.
And that's a lot of
that is, the prerequisite is working
in places that you hate
and the person you're working under
treats you like shit, but you don't, you're not reactionary.
You're taking lessons away without letting your ego say,
wow, he's talking to me a certain way.
Just do your job and I promise you,
you're going to start to
ratchet up the hierarchy.
Your skillset and the people that are treating you bad
will start to respect you and respect your work ethic.
You can't react and be emotional.
The best thing I can tell you,
your viewers, is don't be emotional.
Don't feed your emotions.
Got amazing advice, man.
So where do we find you guys?
The School of Hard Knocks on all platforms.
Yeah, we got a channel.
You think we could see some of that?
You guys going to post something?
Oh, for sure, yeah.
The School of Hard Knocks, boy.
You're going to be famous, man.
So at first I thought
my guy wanted to square up
and fight me, but he
ends up giving an amazing, amazing,
an amazing interview.
Guy made 12 to $15 million in a single year
and just dropped some serious thoughts for you guys.
The two biggest things came
towards the end of that interview
when he said, the secret to becoming successful
is learning how to communicate
and never showing emotion in business.
Great interview out here in New York City.
This video keeps getting better and better.
Let's go get this next one out here.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Real quick, I started a channel in Austin, Texas.
I grew up to 9 million followers.
I go all over the country asking
for business owners their best advice to new entrepreneurs.
Could I get one quick minute with you?
What do you want to know?
What line of business were you in?
Real estate.
Finance.
Yeah?
Yeah, and some other things, too.
Are you a business owner?
Yes, I am.
How long have you been an entrepreneur for?
Myself?
Well, it's been in my family since 1945.
My grandfather bought it.
And then I saw I got into some other things.
I don't want to say how
long I've been in other things, but.
What's your main business?
It's real estate and finance.
Commercial?
I'm a real estate trader.
An options trader.
Actually, let me ask you this.
What was the best financial advice
that you ever received throughout your career?
If there's a lesson about money a
mentor taught you that always stuck with you,
what's that advice you'd give to
people that may not have it?
Well, I'm a home gamer, okay?
So I worked out in my own apartment, okay?
And I worked through, traded through a big company.
Best investment I ever made, best trades I
ever made was a couple of years back,
Amazon.
That was my cash cow.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Did you make a lot of money off of Amazon?
I did, yeah.
You are a trader though, like, like you should.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, what separates the top
1% of traders in today's world?
What do you see that makes the most traders successful?
Determination.
Yeah.
Everyone makes mistakes, me included.
I made mistakes where I got margin calls.
Talk about losing sleep, you know?
It's like the mafia coming after you.
We, you all watched this amount, you know?
Fortunately, I was able to cover it.
Yeah.
Some, Robin Hood.
Remember Robin Hood?
You know Robin Hood?
Remember when the kid, 27, I
think he was 20 years old?
Yeah.
Committed suicide because he, I
knew exactly how he was trading.
Yeah.
And I know why he screwed up.
Right.
And he was not emotionally prepared for
the consequences when he got that margin call.
So I had my share and I go, wow.
So it even makes you a better trader.
You learn from your mistakes if
you know it's your own fault.
And then I, there were times where
I thought about giving up, but I, I,
I just kept going.
And finally it paid off.
And one day, the biggest thrill of my
life was I got invited to a bar.
I was like, I'm going to
New York Stock Exchange for breakfast.
I was like, whoa, me?
And then it was like about 30 of
us through a certain company that we trade through.
I'm not going to say the name.
And it was like the biggest thrill of my life.
And I knew at that point
that I must be doing something right.
You know?
I have back, I'm 70 years old, so
I have back down now a little bit.
But I still do some.
Have you ever been broke before?
No, never been broke.
Never been broke.
What's one lesson about money that
banks don't want people to know?
Well, they would like to take
your money and invest it for you.
You know, I, I don't go through banks.
I do it myself.
You do it yourself.
Yeah. Yeah.
The banks are good for people
who want, you know, like 5%, 6%.
I was making, you know, a lot more than that.
I'm not going to say how much.
I was making a lot more than that.
Give me a range. How much?
A lot.
Yeah.
Yeah?
No.
But it's, look, I live
in Manhattan, you know, some place.
And all through my trading, I have
a year and a half of college.
That's it.
Yeah.
You know, but, but the key is determination.
You never give up.
One day you fall on your face, you get
back up and you do it all over again.
Let me ask you this.
I'm, I'm just.
You're 22.
Yeah.
You're 70.
Whose generation works harder, yours or mine?
Well, look, you want to know about my life?
My grandfather was a coal miner when
he came from this country from Italy.
Nobody worked like he did.
He lost body parts on the job.
You know, my mother was born
in a coal mining country, you know.
So when they came to Brooklyn in the
1930s, my grandfather then worked on the infrastructure
of the city, the bridges and tunnels.
He was the toughest guy I know.
No one to the smallest.
No, as I'm concerned, he went through
the great, they went through the Great Depression.
Nothing.
You either worked or you starved.
There was no, you know, aid
to help you out or whatever.
It was a completely different world.
Here's the difference between myself and your generation.
When I was 22 years old, we didn't, the
stock market was for people who knew someone that
had a friend that worked for a company or
a bank, you know, and that's how you got into
it slowly but surely.
But today with the, with the internet.
Yeah.
It changed everything.
At least it did for me.
You know, I started trading on the internet back
in the late 90s, you know, little by little,
little by little, and all
of a sudden it just snowballed.
That's why I tell all the young
guys, you know, get in it now.
You know, we're not at a
hundred bucks here, a hundred bucks there.
You'd be surprised what that's going to
happen like 30, 40 years from now.
Thank you, my friend.
I appreciate you.
Thank you so much for your time.
This video was amazing, you guys.
I cannot believe some of the people we ran
into out here, but I need you guys to like
and subscribe for amazing content
we've got coming very soon.
And if you're not a member, you're not a member.
You need to join my private entrepreneur
community because guys, mentorship is the only secret
and shortcut to success in today's world.
If you guys want to hop on live
calls and ask your questions directly to the millionaires
and the billionaires that I interview about
how you can start building generational wealth,
how to scale that business or get out of
that nine to five and start and grow that business
or learn the fundamental skills
like sales, negotiations, marketing, everything.
You need to be a member of my community
to join, go to the link down in the description
of this video.
I can't wait to see you on the
inside of the school of mentors, my school community.
With that being said, we'll
see you in the next video.